



Gabriele Scarparo

Nationality: Italian Date of birth: 29/04/1985, Rome

07 67 24 96 55 <u>gabrielescarparo@yahoo.com</u>

Address: 31, Blvd André Netwiller -

www.linkedin.com/in/gabriele-scarparo

Passionate about computer science and history, I have always been interested in the world of books, computers and writing. After my university studies in History and Anthropology, obtained with honors, I collaborated with several websites and cultural research organizations. I have been working in the world of computer science for some years. I am currently a Microsoft Dynamics 365 technical consultant.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2021 - Milan, Italy - Boolean Tech Academy

TRAINING COURSE - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

2021 - Coursera.org - Johns Hopkins University

TRAINING COURSE - FRONT END DEVELOPER - HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

2014 - Rome, Italy - University of Rome LA SAPIENZA - Final grade: 110/110 Laude

MASTER'S DEGREE IN HISTORICAL, HISTORICAL-RELIGIOUS AND ANTHROPOLOGICAL STUDIES

2006- Romea, Italya - University of Rome LA SAPIENZA - Final grade: 110/110

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN HISTORICAL SCIENCES

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2022 - IN PROGRESS - Rome, Italy

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT DYNAMICS 365 - AGIC TECHNOLOGY

- Management and personalization of CRM Microsoft Dynamics 365.
- Programming languages used: C# JavaScript.

Feb. 2021 - Aug. 2021 - Milan, Italy

JR. FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER - STAGE - BOOLEAN TECH ACADEMY

- Daily projects and use of different programming languages for developers.
- Programming languages used: JavaScript, View.js, PHP, Laravel.

Jun. 2007 - Dec. 2020 - Rome, Italy

BOOKSELLER

- Advice and sale to customers.
- Management of orders, returns and stock.
- Inventory control.

May 2014 - May 2016 - Rome, Italy

EDITOR OF SPORTS AND CULTURAL ARTICLES

- Collaborator and editor of sporting articles for the official website of the sports club «S.S.Lazio 1900».
- Contributor and editor of cultural articles for the the Italian newspaper «Europa Quotidiano».

Jan. 2012 - May 2012 - Rome, Italy

CENTRAL STATE ARCHIVE - INTERNSHIP

• Computer inventory of documentation concerning different archive sources of the Central State Archive of Rome.



LANGUAGE SKILLS.

Mother tongue: ITALIAN

Other languages:

FRENCH B2 | ENGLISH A2 |

SKILLS

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Power Point | Social Media | Outlook | Microsoft HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | JavaScript | jQuery | View.js | Bootstrap | PHP | Laravel | C# | MySql

Microsoft Dynamics 365 certifications:

- Power Platform Fundamentals PL-900
 - o https://www.credly.com/badges/09630731-caa2-4fed-84ce-e6ca5d132d70/public_url
- Power Platform Functional Consultant PL-200
 - https://www.credly.com/badges/cec58568-bb64-42be-b60a-795966c111a9/public_url
- Power Platform Developer PL-400
 - https://www.credly.com/badges/f24cd843-cf34-4398-9db9-04fb932bbc7e/public_url

MICROSOFT TRANSCRIPT: https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/users/gabrielescarparo-7580/transcript

Repository GitHub: https://github.com/gabrisca?tab=repositories

Site Web: https://gabrisca.github.io

Site Web Wordpress: https://gabrielescarparo.wordpress.com

OTHER SKILLS

- Good communication skills acquired during my experience as a bookseller.
- Coordination of small teams (3-4 resources) during my experience as a bookseller.
- · Adaptability.
- Listening skills.
- · Written and oral communication skills.

PRIZES AND AWARDS

• Literary Prize « City of Castello » 2021 - Non-fiction section.

PUBBLICAZIONI

Title: Tra Rimozione e Oblio. La memoria storica italiana della Seconda guerra mondiale

Publisher : LuoghInteriori EAN : 9788868643430

https://www.luoghinteriori.it/Autori/scarparo-gabriele/

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B